// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "It is a property that depends on the amount of matter.",
    answer: "Extensive Property",
    options: [
      "Extensive Property",
      "Hydrogen Bond",
      "Gravitational Force",
      "Intensive properties"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: " It do not depend on the quantity of matter.",
    answer: "Intensive properties",
    options: [
      "Extensive Property",
      "Intensive properties",
      "SuperStar",
      "Kinetic Energy"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Volume and ____ are examples of extensive property. ",
    answer: "mass",
    options: [
      "Aqueous Solution",
      "characterized matter.",
      "Crystalline Solids",
      "mass"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Intensive properties serve to _______.",
    answer: "Characterized matter.",
    options: [
      "Characterized matter.",
      "Saturated Solution",
      "Solute",
      "Sinigang Mix"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Weight and length are examples of what? ",
    answer: "extensive property ",
    options: [
      "extensive property ",
      "Gauss' Law",
      "Concentrated Solution",
      "Dilute Solution"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 6,
    question: "It is an example of intensive property. ",
    answer: "Color",
    options: [
      "Color",
      "Weight",
      "Amorphous solid",
      "length"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "True or False: Boiling point is an example of extensive property. ",
    answer: "False",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False",
      ".",
      "."
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 8,
    question: "One example of intensive property is?",
    answer: "Temperature",
    options: [
      "Solid",
      "Weight",
      "Kadita",
      "Temperature"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Hardness is an example of? ",
    answer: "Intensive properties",
    options: [
      "Intensive properties",
      "Extensive Property",
      "Milk Tae",
      "Vapour Pressure"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 10,
    question: "Taste is an example of? ",
    answer: "Intensive properties",
    options: [
      "Intensive properties",
      "Extensive properties",
      "alcohol",
      "Nucleus"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Freezing point is example of? ",
    answer: "Intensive properties",
    options: [
      "Intensive properties",
      "Extensive properties",
      "Anisotrophic",
      "Shapeless"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 12,
    question: "Pressure is?",
    answer: "Intensive properties",
    options: [
      "Intensive properties",
      "Extensive properties",
      "Intramolecular Forces",
      "Negative Force"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Density is an example of?",
    answer: "Intensive properties",
    options: [
      "Intensive properties",
      "Extensive properties",
      "amorphous",
      "Gas"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 14,
    question: "Where is extensive property depends on?",
    answer: "amount of matter",
    options: [
      "Experiment",
      "quality",
      "amount of matter",
      "Solution"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Which is an example of extensive properties. ",
    answer: "Energy",
    options: [
      "Luffy",
      "Solvent",
      "Naruto",
      "Energy"
    ]
  },
]